Hey and my Marta How is she adapting to
Oye y mi Marta Cómo se está adaptando a
me Marta seems like a discovery to me I
mí Marta me parece un descubrimiento no
couldn't prejudge her for getting to know her From
podía prejuzgar la por conocerla Yo por
what I saw of her to me, well there were
lo que veía de ella a mí pues había
things that made it seem to me that the girl was
cosas que me parecía que estaba la chica
there she was a person who was in
para allá era una persona que estaba
love when you are in love and you are
enamorada cuando estás enamorado y estás
Blinded by love You are crazy, crazy in love,
Ciego de amor Estás loco es loco de amor
the word itself says it and I believe
es que la palabra misma lo dice y yo
that yes, crazy in love even if she doesn't
creo que sí que loca de amor aunque no
say it when you love you love and love doesn't
lo diga cuando amas amas y el amor no
carry and love goes away if it really is
lleva y se va el amor si realmente es
love, love stays and for it to come out you
amor el amor se queda y para que salga
need a lot of time and in the end it won't
necesitas mucho tiempo y al final no
come out completely it will always remain there
saldrá del todo siempre quedará ahí
because it is typical love, love of which there is
porque es amor típico amor del que
always a gap, not Marta's with
siempre hay resquicio no el de Marta con
ant, love whatever it is there is
ant el amor sea el que sea siempre hay
always a gap, the story of now is what
resquicio siempre el relato de ahora es
she truly feels because it is what she
el que ella de verdad siente porque es
feels at this moment I don't know what she will
el que siente en este momento no sé lo
feel in 15 days if you see
que sentirá dentro de 15 días si tú ves
my story of my marriage in 2011 it
mi relato de mi matrimonio en 2011 no
has nothing to do with 2016 Now I
tiene nada que ver con 2016 Ahora yo te
tell you that she still has love
digo que está todavía le queda amor Ya
She can tell me the same thing  you said
me puede decir ella misa se lo dijiste
In fact I won't keep dressing him and
De hecho no se lo seguiré vistiendo y
everything
todo